Aim:

Available prosthetic hands are typically controlled using EMG signals from available arm muscles. However, there are some people who do not have any muscle controls below neck, such as locked in patients, quadriplegic and etc. Therefore this project aims to develop an advanced classification algorithm with corresponded scenarios which will collect EEG signals from human subjects.

 针对相应的应用场景采集到的高静噪比的EEG数据进行分类，从而实现精准的控制


Project Objectives:

1.	Design and implementing a BCI interface to present different stimuli (different motor imagination and grasping functions)
2.	Coupling the designed BCI interface with the EEG device for synchronised EEG recording
3.	Recording EEG data from a number of participants performing different mental imagination including different grasping functions
4.	Developing a classification algorithm to discriminate between grasp imagination and rest
5.	(Advanced) Developing a classification algorithm to discriminate different grasping functions
6.	(Advanced) Implementing the proposed classification algorithm in a online BCI system coupled with a robotic hand
